export default levels = [
  {
    // Level 1
    id: 1,
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Which specie of lion has been extinct?",
        options: ["White Lion", "Asian Lion", "Cave Lions", "African Lions"],
        correctAnswer: "Cave Lions",
      },
      {
        question: "Which animal cannot Jump?",
        options: ["Panda", "Kangaroo", "Giraffe", "Elephant"],
        correctAnswer: "Elephant",
      },
      {
        question: "Most Hardworking animal is?",
        options: ["Camel", "Horse", "Ants", "Non"],
        correctAnswer: "Ants",
      },
      {
        question: "Which animal Sleeps while standing??",
        options: ["Horse", "Buffalo", "Chimpanzee", "Pygmy Marmoset "],
        correctAnswer: "Horse",
      },
      {
        question: "Which animal is so brave?",
        options: ["Wolf ", "Lion", "honey badgers", "Tiger"],
        correctAnswer: "honey badgers",
      },
      {
        question: "Nose prints of which animals are as  unique as Human  fingers ?",
        options: ["Gorillas", " Chimpanzee", "Tiger ", "Pygmy Marmoset "],
        correctAnswer: "Gorillas",
      },
      {
        question: " Which animal has Colorless blood especially when oxygen is removed from Blood?",
        options: ["Crocodile", "starfish", "Icefish", "Whales"],
        correctAnswer: "Icefish",
      },
      {
        question: "Which animal has shortest living span?",
        options: ["honey bee ", "May fly", "Ant", "Mosquito "],
        correctAnswer: "May fly",
      },
      {
        question: "Which land animal has maximum number of teeth?",
        options: ["Armadillo", "Crocodile", "Monkey", "Panda"],
        correctAnswer: "Armadillo",
      },
      {
        question: "How many eggs can a frog lay at one time?",
        options: ["2000-2500", "1500-2000", "3000-4000", "4000-4500"],
        correctAnswer: "3000-4000",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    // Level 2
    id: 2,
    questions: [
      {
        question: "How many types of fishes are found in Sea?",
        options: ["2000", "200", "20000", "5000"],
        correctAnswer: "20000",
      },
      {
        question: "Smallest Monkey of the World is?",
        options: ["Bornean Orangutan", "Pygmy Marmoset", "Chimpanzee", "Rhesus Macaque"],
        correctAnswer: "Pygmy Marmoset",
      },
      {
        question: "Which animal do not have a brain?",
        options: ["Whale ", "Clown Fish", "Snake", "Starfish"],
        correctAnswer: "Starfish",
      },
      {
        question: "Which animal cannot stick their tongue out?",
        options: ["Snake", "Tortoise", "Turtle", "Crocodile"],
        correctAnswer: "Crocodile",
      },
      {
        question: "Which animal has bigger eyes than its brain?",
        options: ["Lion", "Snake", "Ostrich", "Ant"],
        correctAnswer: "Ostrich",
      },
      {
        question: "Which animal can see in all directions at the same time?",
        options: ["Camel", "Dragonflies", "Panda", "Kangaroo"],
        correctAnswer: "Dragonflies",
      },
      {
        question: "Which creature is slowest and lazies?",
        options: ["Ants", "Turtle", "Tortoise", "Toed Sloths"],
        correctAnswer: "Toed Sloths",
      },
      {
        question: "Which is the smartest animal?",
        options: ["Chimpanzee", "Ants", "Tortoise", "Snake"],
        correctAnswer: "Chimpanzee",
      },
      {
        question: "How much food an elephant eats normally in a day?",
        options: ["200kg", "300kg", "130kg", "500kg"],
        correctAnswer: "130kg",
      },
      {
        question: "Average maximum speed of a tortoise is?",
        options: ["0.5km/hr", "1.01km/hr", "0.2km/hr", "2km/hr"],
        correctAnswer: "1.01km/hr",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    // Level 3
    id: 3,
    questions: [
      {
        question: "What is average age of a tiger?",
        options: ["10-12 Years ", "16-18 Years", "18-20 Years ", "14-16 Years"],
        correctAnswer: "14-16 Years",
      },
      {
        question: "How many species of Lion has been extinct?",
        options: ["One Species", "Two Species", "Four Species", "Non"],
        correctAnswer: "Four Species",
      },
      {
        question: "How many dogs are present in the world?",
        options: ["400 Million", "570 Million", "370 Million", "470 Million"],
        correctAnswer: "470 Million",
      },
      {
        question: "Maximum weight of salt water crocodile is?",
        options: ["1000 kg", "500 kg", "250 kg", "700 kg"],
        correctAnswer: "1000 kg",
      },
      {
        question: "Which animals burp when they are happy?",
        options: ["Chimpanzee", "Gorillas", "Pigmy Marmoset", "Non"],
        correctAnswer: "Gorillas",
      },
      {
        question: "which animal lays biggest eggs in the world?",
        options: ["Ostrich", "Crocodile", "Jelly Fish", "Sharks"],
        correctAnswer: "Sharks",
      },
      {
        question: "Which animal has three hearts?",
        options: ["Octopus", "Squids", "Cuttlefish", "All of these"],
        correctAnswer: "All of these",
      },
      {
        question: "A Tigers Roar can be heared as far as how many Kilometers?",
        options: ["Three", "Five", "Two", "Six"],
        correctAnswer: "Three",
      },
      {
        question: "Giant Anteaters can eat how many insects a day?",
        options: ["30000", "2000", "200", "1500"],
        correctAnswer: "30000",
      },
      {
        question: "Which animal has no blood?",
        options: ["Whale", "Starfish", "Both", "Non"],
        correctAnswer: "Starfish",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    // Level 4
    id: 4,
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Where does fertilization takes place in frogs?",
        options: ["Land", "Ocean", "Dessert", "Water"],
        correctAnswer: "Water",
      },
      {
        question: "Guinea pigs eat?",
        options: ["Meat", "Bones", "Flesh", "Grass"],
        correctAnswer: "Grass",
      },
      {
        question: "Normal temperature of a bird is?",
        options: ["106 F", "101 F", "102 F", "103 F"],
        correctAnswer: "106 F",
      },
      {
        question: "The insect  which has the largest population on Earth is?",
        options: ["goby", "reptile", "cockroach", "wasp"],
        correctAnswer: "wasp",
      },
      {
        question: "Largest kangaroo in the world is?",
        options: ["brown kangaroo", " red kangaroo", "both", "non"],
        correctAnswer: "red kangaroo",
      },
      {
        question: "The largest of a lizards is?",
        options: ["dragonfly", "varanids", "anguimorphs", "komodo dragon"],
        correctAnswer: "komodo dragon",
      },
      {
        question: "The largest flying mammal is the one?",
        options: ["mice", "dragonfly", "grasshopper", "mouse eared bat"],
        correctAnswer: "mouse eared bat",
      },
      {
        question: "The tallest living animal is?",
        options: ["Ostrich", "Giraffe", "Cow", "Camel"],
        correctAnswer: "Giraffe",
      },
      {
        question: "Markhor are important for its?",
        options: ["Horns", "Slin", "Hooves", "Eyes"],
        correctAnswer: "Horns",
      },
      {
        question: "Guinea pig is a__^^!?",
        options: ["Bird", "Amphibian", "Reptile", "Mammal"],
        correctAnswer: "Mammal",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    // Level 5
    id: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Baby bird is referred as?",
        options: ["Kittens", "Moans", "Nestlings", "Non"],
        correctAnswer: "Nestlings",
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following is a mammal?",
        options: ["Crocodile", "Turtle", "Dolphin", "Shark"],
        correctAnswer: "Dolphin",
      },
      {
        question: "Shape of testes in male frog?",
        options: ["Spherical", "Triangular", "Ovoid", "Irregular"],
        correctAnswer: "Ovoid",
      },
      {
        question: "Which one is not a functional ear in frog?",
        options: ["Defense", "Hearing", "Balance", "All"],
        correctAnswer: "Defense",
      },
      {
        question: "Bird is a ___ blooded animal?",
        options: ["Cold", "Moderate", "Warm", "Non"],
        correctAnswer: "Warm",
      },
      {
        question: "Lifespan of Guinea pigs?",
        options: ["2 years", "5 to 8 years", "7 years", "10 years"],
        correctAnswer: "5 to 8 years",
      },
      {
        question: "Number of elephant species in the World:?",
        options: ["2", "5", "7", "3"],
        correctAnswer: "3",
      },
      {
        question: "Group of elephants is known as?",
        options: ["Pride", "Colony", "Herd", "Caravan"],
        correctAnswer: "Herd",
      },
      {
        question: "The smallest eggs are being laid by which type of bird?",
        options: ["HummingBird", "Ostrich", "Peacock", "Falcon"],
        correctAnswer: "HummingBird",
      },
      {
        question: "Which of these is not a marine mammal?",
        options: ["Dolphin", "Komodo dragon", "Seal", "Whale"],
        correctAnswer: "Komodo dragon",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    // Level 6
    id: 6,
    questions: [
      {
        question: "This is the most important mammalian character of rat is?",
        options: ["Mammary Glands", "Pinna", "Paws", "Hair"],
        correctAnswer: "Mammary Glands",
      },
      {
        question: "In the mammal body the largest gland is?",
        options: ["pituitary", "pancreas", "thyroid", "liver"],
        correctAnswer: "liver",
      },
      {
        question: "Peacocks Happy to stay?",
        options: ["Alone", "In groups", "In herd", "Non"],
        correctAnswer: "In groups",
      },
      {
        question: "  ____ bird mimic the humans?",
        options: ["Parrots", "Aves", "Robbin", "Sparrow"],
        correctAnswer: "Parrots",
      },
      {
        question: "Fastest speed of at which the elephant can run?",
        options: ["25 mph", "15 mph", "24 mph", "35 mph"],
        correctAnswer: "25 mph",
      },
      {
        question: "Bird having longest lifespan is?",
        options: ["Falcon", "Eagle", "Robbin", "Large Parrot"],
        correctAnswer: "Large Parrot",
      },
      {
        question: "which bird can only eat when its head is upside down?",
        options: ["flamingo", "American robin", "ostrich", "falcon"],
        correctAnswer: "flamingo",
      },
      {
        question: "What kind of training are elephants widely provided?",
        options: ["to act in circus", "to lift heavy load", "non", "both first and second"],
        correctAnswer: "both first and second",
      },
      {
        question: "These teeth are not found in rat?",
        options: ["Molars", "Canines", "Premolars", "Canines and Premolars"],
        correctAnswer: "Canines and Premolars",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the tallest bird in the world?",
        options: ["Penguin", "Ostrich", "Emu", "Crane"],
        correctAnswer: "Emu",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    // Level 7
    id: 7,
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Which animal only move the back legs together on land, but can kick each leg independently in the water to swim?",
        options: ["Cheetah", "Cobra", "Perl", "Kangaroos"],
        correctAnswer: "Kangaroos",
      },
      {
        question: "Which type of deer has a long lifespan?",
        options: ["moose ", "roe deer", "axis deer ", "all"],
        correctAnswer: "axis deer ",
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following big cat cannot roar?",
        options: ["Cheetah", "Wild Leopard", "Tiger", "Snow Leopard"],
        correctAnswer: "Snow Leopard",
      },
      {
        question: "How long does it normally take for a sloth to digest all the food?",
        options: ["1 week", "2 weeks", "3 weeks", "4 weeks"],
        correctAnswer: "4 weeks",
      },
      {
        question: "Which word is used to call a group of sharks?",
        options: ["Sharklet", "Shoal", "Flotilla", "all"],
        correctAnswer: "Shoal",
      },
      {
        question: "What is stored in the hump of a camel?",
        options: ["Fat", "Water", "Protein", "Food"],
        correctAnswer: "Fat",
      },
      {
        question: "In which of the following animals do the males give birth?",
        options: ["Dragonfly", "Shrimp", "Sea Dragon", "All"],
        correctAnswer: "Sea Dragon",
      },
      {
        question: "After successful hunting, which lion in the group tends to eat first?",
        options: ["Females", "Cubs", "Males", "Whole Group"],
        correctAnswer: "Males",
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following is the only bird specie that can fly backward?",
        options: ["hummingbird", " scarlet robin", "falcon", "turkey"],
        correctAnswer: "hummingbird",
      },
      {
        question: "Bones in Horse?",
        options: ["205", "206", "207", "208"],
        correctAnswer: "205",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    // Level 8
    id: 8,
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Scales in rat are present on?",
        options: ["Head", "Abdomen", "Neck", "Tail"],
        correctAnswer: "Tail",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the color of polar bear skin?",
        options: ["White", "Brown", "Black", "Silver"],
        correctAnswer: "Black",
      },
      {
        question: "Common brown rat is?",
        options: ["Rattus meltada", "Rattus norvegicus", "Rattus rattus", "Non"],
        correctAnswer: "Rattus norvegicus",
      },
      {
        question: "How many male lions are in a pride?",
        options: ["upto 4", "upto 3", "upto 2", "more than 3"],
        correctAnswer: "upto 3",
      },
      {
        question: "Lions are related to which specie?",
        options: ["Amphibians ", "Reptiles", "Cats", "Non"],
        correctAnswer: "Cats",
      },
      {
        question: "What is hippocampus?",
        options: ["Sea Horse", "Wild Horse", "Horse", "All"],
        correctAnswer: "Sea Horse",
      },
      {
        question: "A baby dairy cow is known as?",
        options: ["Lamb", "Shamp", "Baby", "Calf"],
        correctAnswer: "Calf",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the largest single part of all living organisms?",
        options: ["Protein", "Nutrients", "Water", "Skin"],
        correctAnswer: "Water",
      },
      {
        question: "Which is the biggest organ in chickens?",
        options: ["Liver", "Heart", "Eyes", "Lungs"],
        correctAnswer: "Liver",
      },
      {
        question: "Which one of the following is not a true snake?",
        options: ["Blind Snake", "Glass Snake", "Sea Snake", "Tree Snake"],
        correctAnswer: "Glass Snake",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    // Level 9
    id: 9,
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Characteristic of Camel is?",
        options: ["Harelip", "Third Eyelid", "Short Eye", "Non"],
        correctAnswer: "Third Eyelid",
      },
      {
        question: "Female Fox is called?",
        options: ["Mare", "Vixen", "Wolf", "Non"],
        correctAnswer: "Vixen",
      },
      {
        question: "Most popular non vegetarian food includes?",
        options: ["Beef", "Chicken", "Turkeys", "Mutton"],
        correctAnswer: "Chicken",
      },
      {
        question: "The deadliest creature in the world is?",
        options: ["Mosquitos", "Testes Fly", "Sea Creature", "Non"],
        correctAnswer: "Mosquitos",
      },
      {
        question: "Which large mammal has a tail so it can stand on it and lift its back legs off the ground?",
        options: ["Kangaroo", "Camel", "Sheep", "Monkey"],
        correctAnswer: "Kangaroo",
      },
      {
        question: "How many Camel species exist?",
        options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
        correctAnswer: "2",
      },
      {
        question: "White breed of Goat is called as?",
        options: ["Sannen", "Wild", "Carnivorus", "Herbivorus"],
        correctAnswer: "Sannen",
      },
      {
        question: "Fishs are categorised in.....?",
        options: ["Cold Blooded", "Warm Blooded", "Moderate", "Non"],
        correctAnswer: "Cold Blooded",
      },
      {
        question: "The national animal of Pakistan is...!?",
        options: ["Snake ", "Falcon", "Markhor", "Non"],
        correctAnswer: "Markhor",
      },
      {
        question: "Which animal is called Royal animal?",
        options: ["Cat", "Dog", "Lion", "Horse"],
        correctAnswer: "Horse",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    // Level 10
    id: 10,
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Baby rabbit is called as..!?",
        options: ["Buck", "Doe", "Kitten", "Cub"],
        correctAnswer: "Kitten",
      },
      {
        question: "Camel can drink up to ..... Gallon of water in 10 minutes.?",
        options: ["30", "50", "80", "85"],
        correctAnswer: "30",
      },
      {
        question: "A baby camel can fully walk within...!?",
        options: ["After 1 hour", "Within half an hour", "After 1.5 hour", "Within 10 minutes"],
        correctAnswer: "Within half an hour",
      },
      {
        question: "Markhor belongs to which specie?",
        options: ["Wild Buffalo", "Wild Goat", "Sheep", "Non"],
        correctAnswer: "Wild Goat",
      },
      {
        question: "The large animal virus is?",
        options: ["Pox", "Herpes", "Adeno", "Picorna"],
        correctAnswer: "Pox",
      },
      {
        question: "kangaroos are:?",
        options: ["Omnivore", "Carnivore", "Herbivore", "Non"],
        correctAnswer: "Herbivore",
      },
      {
        question: "Most common breed of cattle is?",
        options: ["Holstein", "Jersey", "Brown Swiss", "Non"],
        correctAnswer: "Holstein",
      },
      {
        question: "Horses most prefer to?",
        options: ["Live alone ", "Live in groups", "Live with friends", "Non"],
        correctAnswer: "Live in groups",
      },
      {
        question: "How long is an elephant pregnant before it gives birth?",
        options: ["18 months", "19 months", "22 months", "24 months"],
        correctAnswer: "22 months",
      },
      {
        question: "Who is the most intelligent animal?",
        options: ["Dolphin", "Lion", "Cat", "Tiger"],
        correctAnswer: "Dolphin",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    // Level 11
    id: 11,
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Size of new-born kangaroo...!?",
        options: ["0.25 inch", "0.75 inch", "1 inch", "Non"],
        correctAnswer: "1 inch",
      },
      {
        question: "which one is the fastest land animal?",
        options: ["Lion", "Giraffe", "Markhor", "Cheetah"],
        correctAnswer: "Cheetah",
      },
      {
        question: "Which Mammal can fly?",
        options: ["Squirrels", "foxes", "Sugar Glider", "Bats"],
        correctAnswer: "Bats",
      },
      {
        question: "How many humps does a Bactrian  camel have?",
        options: ["1", "2", "3", "0"],
        correctAnswer: "2",
      },
      {
        question: "which animal eats mainly bamboo?",
        options: ["Giraffe", "Beer", "Panda", "Goat"],
        correctAnswer: "Panda",
      },
      {
        question: "Main reason of the decline in wildlife populations?",
        options: ["Falling of trees", "paucity of drinking water", "Floods", "habitat destruction"],
        correctAnswer: "habitat destruction",
      },
      {
        question: "Which vertebrate category contains the most endangered  species?",
        options: ["Mammals", "Fishes", "Reptiles", "Non"],
        correctAnswer: "Mammals",
      },
      {
        question: "which animal is known to be the mans best friend?",
        options: ["Cat", "Dog", "Horse", "Fish"],
        correctAnswer: "Dog",
      },
      {
        question: "what is the name of baby horse?",
        options: ["Lamb", "Doe", "Boar", "Foal"],
        correctAnswer: "Foal",
      },
      {
        question: "Which sense of tiger is most highly developed?",
        options: ["Touch", "Hearing", "Smell", "Sight"],
        correctAnswer: "Hearing",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    // Level 12
    id: 12,
    questions: [
      {
        question: "which of the following animal would you not expect in a dairy farm?",
        options: ["Cattle", "Buffalo", "Camel", "Sheep"],
        correctAnswer: "Camel",
      },
      {
        question: "shape of tigers pupils?",
        options: ["Square", "Rectangular", "Triangular", "Circular"],
        correctAnswer: "Circular",
      },
      {
        question: "Scrotum is absent in?",
        options: ["Stallion", "Cock", "Boar", "Roam"],
        correctAnswer: "Cock",
      },
      {
        question: "Lion is known as the?",
        options: ["King of Sky", "King of Sea", "King of Animals", "King of Jungle"],
        correctAnswer: "King of Jungle",
      },
      {
        question: "Horses hair is known as?",
        options: ["Wool", "Mane", "Ferrier", "Non"],
        correctAnswer: "Mane",
      },
      {
        question: "which part of the body used by tiger for cleaning?",
        options: ["Tongue", "Mane", "Lips", "Toes"],
        correctAnswer: "Tongue",
      },
      {
        question: "Piglet is the baby of which animal?",
        options: ["Cow", "Sheep", "Camel", "Pig"],
        correctAnswer: "Pig",
      },
      {
        question: "Whom did the animals start to work for?",
        options: ["Man", "Themselves", "Djinn", "Non"],
        correctAnswer: "Man",
      },
      {
        question: "Which animal can stand on its tail?",
        options: ["Cattle", "Monkey", "Crocodile", "Kangaroo"],
        correctAnswer: "Kangaroo",
      },
      {
        question: "What kind of animal is a komodo dragon?",
        options: ["rat", "fish", "lizard", "Snake"],
        correctAnswer: "lizard",
      },
    ],
  },
];
